你们一定不敢不信
You're not gonna believe this.
我编了一则笑话寄到《花花公子》
I made up a joke and sent it in to Playboy.
结果登出来了
They printed it.
我不知道《花花公子》也登笑话
I didn't know they print jokes.
他们有笑话  专访  扎实的新闻报导
They print jokes, interviews, hard-hitting journalism.
并非只有裸女图片
It's not just about the pictures.
当年妈不信你  现在我们也不可能会信
Didn't work on Mom, it's not gonna work on us.
给  你们看  还是第一则呢
Here, check it out. It's the first one, too.
在这里
Right there.
真好笑
That is funny.
我编出来时也很好笑
It was also funny when I made it up.
-什么  -这则笑话是我编的
- What? - I made that joke up.
不是你  是我
No, you didn't. I did.
是我  我说给公司的丹听
Yes, I did. I told it to Dan at work,
他说这是他听过最好笑的笑话
and he said it was the funniest joke he'd ever heard.
帮我谢谢丹
Hey, tell Dan thanks.
怎样
What?
抱歉  我在看下面那则笑话
I'm sorry, I was just reading the joke below it.
那则很好笑
Man, that one is funny.
莫妮卡  你记得我跟你说过那则笑话吧
Monica, you remember me telling you that joke, right?
-不记得  -真不记得吗
- No. - Seriously?
你的笑话一大堆
You tell a lot of jokes.
钱德勒  那是我的笑话
Look, Chandler, it's my joke.
不过他们没有印投稿人的名字
But if it makes you feel any better,
或者这样你会好过点
they don't print the name.
所以是谁的并不重要  对吧
So it doesn't really matter who gets credit.
大概吧
Yeah, I guess.
-你们好  -乔伊  《花花公子》登了我的笑话
- Hey, guys. - Playboy printed my joke!
不  不  那是我的笑话
No, no, it's mine, it's my joke.
你可以打电话去问  他们会告诉你是谁的
You can call them, they'll tell you.
-那是我的笑话  -是我的
- It's my joke! - It's my joke!
笑话
Jokes? What...?
你们知道这上面有裸女吧
You guys know they have naked chicks in there, right?
快  赶快转到《音乐幕后》
Dude! You have got to turn on Behind The Music.
红心合唱团状况百出  可能会解散
The band Heart is having a tough time and they may break up.
我们去你家看吧
Let's watch that at your place.
不行  莫妮卡在看烹饪节目
Nah, Monica's watching some cooking show.
快点  我可不想错过第一手消息
Come on, I don't want to miss when they were skinny.
钱德勒  你知道吗
Chandler, Chandler, You know what we should do?
我们应该去买新墨镜
You and I should go out and get some new sunglasses.
什么  不要  我想看电视
What? No, I want to watch this.
你的有线电视断线了吗
Did your cable go out?
不是  那是热门音乐台
No. No, that's VH1 .
我跟你说  现在小孩听的音乐
I tell you, the music these kids listen to today...
我都觉得好吵哦
It's like a lotta noise to me. I don't know...
乔伊  为什么你有线台没了
Joey, why is your cable out?
因为我没交钱
Because, uh, I haven't really paid the bill
你若缺钱
If you need money,
拜托让我借给你点  好吗
would you please-please just let me loan you some money?
不要  钱德勒  你别再说了
No, Chandler. Look, forget about it, okay?
我知道吉宁搬走后  我手头是有点紧
I know things have been tight since Janine moved out.
天哪  她可真辣
God, was she hot.
就是啊
I know, yeah.
但是我可以应付  好吗
Look, I can handle it, all right?
我可以听广播
I can listen to the radio.
罗斯也给了我一本很棒的书
And Ross gave me this great book.
要不要问那个笑话小偷
You want to see if the joke stealer
我们能不能去他家看
will let us watch the show at his place?
好啊
Sure.
-电话费有缴吗  -没有
- Paid your phone bill? - Not so much.
原来是你
It's only you.
你们在看什么
What are you doing?
我们在看《花花公子》
Looking at a Playboy.
我也想看
I want to look too!
哎哟
Yikes!
你们认为
So do you think that these pictures-
这些照片是有故事性的吗
Are, are they trying to tell a story?
当然有
Oh, yeah, sure.
比如像这位年轻小姐
I mean, like in the case of this young woman,
她的衣服不见了  所以...
...she has lost her clothes, so...
她光溜溜的骑着马
So she rides naked on the horse,
大喊"我的衣服呢  我的衣服呢"
she's crying out, "Where are they? Where are they?"
撩人地躺在草地上  是找不到的
She's not gonna find them, lying in the grass like that.
记不记得以前去马厩
Remember the days when you'd go out to the barn...
掀起衣服翘起屁股的日子吗
...lift up your shirt and bend over?
我会愿意约这个女孩出去
You see, now, I would date this girl.
她很可爱  很阳光
She's cute, she's outdoorsy.
她知道怎样点火
You know, and she knows how to build a fire.
总会有用上她的一天
I mean, that's got to come in handy.
我有一个问题
I got a question.
如果要在我们之中挑女朋友
If you had to pick one of us to date,
你们会挑谁
who would it be?
-不知道  -我也不知道
- I don't know. - Me neither.
瑞秋
Rachel.
什么
What?
不知道
I don't know.
我也不知道
Me neither.
红心合唱团有多少经典的歌啊
You know, you forget how many great songs Heart had.
《梭子鱼》是我学会弹的第一首歌
"Barracuda" was the first song I learned to play on the keyboard.
那么说你听过  弹过
So you heard it, you repeated it...
所以那首歌是你写的咯
...so that must mean you wrote it.
你们怎么还争啊  老实说
You guys with this joke. Well, I gotta say...
尽管我当时捧腹大笑
...l know I cracked up,
但我不确定有没有看懂
but I'm not even sure I got it.
什么
What?
你看不懂
You didn't get it?
那个医生是只猴子
The doctor is a monkey.
猴子没办法开处方
And monkeys can't write out prescriptions.
我的笑话不准你笑
You are not allowed to laugh at my joke.
你的笑话
Your joke?
海夫纳可不会同意[花花公子创办人]
Well, I think the Hef would disagree.
所以他寄了这张
Which is why he sent me a check...
百元支票给我
...for $ 100.
你偷我的笑话  还偷我的钱
So you stole my joke and you stole my money?
我本来要拿去存款机存的
I was gonna stick it in the ATM.
现在我决定让那位性感女行员
But now I think I'll show the sexy teller...
知道我是个作家
...that I am a published writer.
她会知道你是偷来的
Well, she is going to know that you stole the joke.
你想怎样  跟着我去吗
Oh, what are you going to do, follow me down there?
-没错  -反正我现在又不去
- Yeah. - Well, I'm not going to go now anyway
好
Okay.
帐单
Here you go.
甘瑟
Gunther?
我现在没钱付  因为我没工作
I can't pay now, because I'm not working.
因而我必须尽量避免奢侈行为
I've had to cut down on some luxuries like...
像付帐之类的
...paying for stuff, so....
如果你不介意  你可以来这里工作
Well, if you want, you can work here.
我不晓得...
I don't know.
只是
It's just....
我是连续剧的常驻演员
See, I was a regular on a soap opera, you know?
从明星到服务员  我实在...
And to go from that to this, it's just....
而且还得给我朋友端茶送水
And plus, I'd have to wait on all my friends.
好  但薪水不错哦
Okay. But the money's good.
还可以看瑞秋看个够
Plus, you get to stare at Rachel as much as you want.
什么
What?
工作时间很弹性
Flexible hours.
也许我可以当个服务员
Maybe I could be a waiter.
可以用电话吗
Could I use the phone?
她选了瑞秋
She picked Rachel.
虽然她想改口  但是很明显
I mean, she tried to back out of it, but it was obvious.
她选瑞秋
She picked Rachel.
他偷我的笑话  还那么理所当然
He took my joke. He just took it.
这样是不对的  你知道还有什么是不对的吗
This is wrong. You know what else is wrong?
菲比选了瑞秋
Phoebe picking Rachel.
还有谁会选瑞秋吗  罗斯
Know who else picked Rachel? Ross.
罗斯还做了什么  他偷了我的笑话
You know what else Ross did? He stole my joke.
我要买一本笑话日志
You know what? I'm going to get a joke journal.
好记录我每次讲笑话的日期时间
And document the date and time of every single one of my jokes.
好主意  你知道什么主意不好吗
Good idea. Know what's a bad idea?
-选择瑞秋  -没错
- Picking Rachel. - That's right.
什么声音
Did you hear something?
也许是罗斯爬进我的脑袋
Maybe it's the sound of Ross climbing into my brain
窃取我的思绪
to steal my thoughts.
是从客厅传来的
It's coming from the living room.
我的书看完了
I finished my book.
-姐妹们 -好啊
- Hey, you guys. - Hey.
你们好可爱
Don't you guys look cute.
真是可爱的一对
You guys make a cute couple.
莫妮卡  你这是在干嘛
Monica, what are you doing?
没什么  我只是想再造出
Nothing, I'm just trying to recreate some of the fun that
我们前两天的欢乐时光
we had at my place the other day.
就是你选瑞秋不选我那次
Remember? When you picked Rachel over me?
蛮好玩的
That was funny.
-是挺好玩的  -一点也不好玩
- lt was kind of funny. - lt wasn't funny at all!
你为什么选她
Why would you do that?
为什么不选我
Why? Why didn't you pick me?
好
Fine.
我之所以比较倾向瑞秋
The reason that I was leaning a little bit more toward Rachel than you
是因为你...
...is just, you know, you're...
有点难搞
...kinda high maintenance
我们去吃饭吧
Okay, let's go to lunch!
哪有这回事
That is completely untrue.
你觉得我难搞
You think I'm high maintenance?
证明给我看
Okay, prove it.
你列一张清单  我们逐条讨论
I want write out a list, and we'll go through it point by point.
你说得对  你很好相处
No, you're right, you're easygoing.
你只是没有瑞秋那么好相处
You're just not as easygoing as Rachel.
她比较有弹性  比较圆滑
She's just more flexible and-and mellow.
就这样
That's all.
每个人都不一样
Well, people are different.
瑞秋什么都好
Rachel will do whatever you want.
怎么欺负她都行
You can just walk all over her.
慢着
What? Wait a minute.
你是说我没个性吗
Are you saying that I'm a pushover?
我才不是
I'm not a pushover.
好  你有个性
Oh, okay. You're not a pushover.
天哪  你觉得我没个性
You think I'm a pushover.
好吧  你听着  我们不跟你吃饭了
Well wait, watch this, you know what? You're not invited to lunch.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think of that?
我觉得够强硬了吧
I think that's pretty strong, that's what I think.
走  莫妮卡  我们去吃饭
Come on, Monica, let's go to lunch.
把清单给我列出来
You start working on that list.
她真是太扯了
I cannot believe her.
就是啊  你想去哪里吃饭
I know. Where do you want to go eat?
我很喜欢那家日本料理
Oh, I love that Japanese place.
我吃腻日本菜了  不去
I'm sick of Japanese. Not going there.
好吧  你想去哪里就去哪里
All right. Wherever you want to go is cool.
甘瑟
Oh, hey, Gunther...
你看
...check this out.
那个钱德勒讲的超好笑
Yeah, that Chandler cracks me up.
罗斯  你要喝什么吗
Hey Ross, listen, you want anything to drink,
我正好要去柜台
'cause I'm heading up there.
-要  我要咖啡  谢了  -不客气
- I'll take a coffee. Thanks. - Sure.
-咖啡  -不要
- Coffee? - No.
要咖啡吗  我要去柜台
Coffee? I'm going up there.
不用了
No, thank you.
需要什么吗  我要去柜台
You need anything? I'm heading up there.
我要一杯冰水
I'd love ice water.
没问题
You got it.
乔伊  你在干什么
Joey, what are you doing?
以示友善啊
Just being friendly.
乔伊  亲爱的  你不能去柜台后面
Joey, honey, I don't think you're supposed to go back there.
没关系啦  对吧  甘瑟
Nah, it's okay. Right, Gunther?
别跟我使眼色
Don't wink at me.
把围裙穿上
And put on your apron.
穿就穿
Okay.
你怎么不叫其他客人穿围裙
I don't see you asking other paying customers to put on aprons.
-乔伊  你在这里打工吗  -没有
- Joey, do you work here? - No.
-服务员  -什么事
- Waiter. - Yeah!
乔伊  怎么回事
Joey, What's going on?
你为什么不告诉我们  你在这里工作
Why didn't you tell us you work here?
这件事蛮尴尬的
It's kind of embarrassing.
我之前是演员  现在是服务员
I mean, I was an actor, now I'm a waiter.
这有点背道而驰
It's supposed to go the other direction.
就象你的围裙  它现在成了个披风
So's your apron. You're wearing it like a cape.
这份工作很简单  薪水很高
I mean, the job's easy and the money's good, you know?
反正我都在这混
I guess I'm going to be hanging out here anyway.
干脆赚个钱呗
I might as well get paid for it, right?
只是要招呼你们感觉很怪
I just feel kind of weird serving you guys, you know?
会好起来的
It'll be great.
乔伊  我也做过  其实也还好啊
Come on, Joey, I did it and it was fine.
对啊  怎么会怪
Why would it be weird?
乔伊  给我来杯咖啡
Hey, Joey? Can I get some coffee?
好吧  确实没那么怪
Okay, I guess it doesn't seem that weird.
我说真的  我早就点了  现在还没端来
Seriously, I-I asked you before and you still haven't gotten it.
现在又变怪了
See, now it's weird again.
你来这里工作是好事
I think it's great that you work here.
你会赚大钱  给你第一笔忠告[小费]
You're gonna make a lot of money. Here's your first tip.
那就是别吃黄雪
Don't eat yellow snow.
2点15分  咖啡馆
2:15, coffeehouse.
太好了
Well, you know what? This is great.
总算有人能传承我的智慧
Finally, someone I can pass my wisdom to.
告诉你几条我在这里工作时
Let me tell you about a couple of things I learned
学到的经验
while working at the coffeehouse.
首先  顾客永远是对的
First of all, the customer is always right.
微笑能让你无往不利
A smile goes a long way.
有人对你不客气  就朝松饼打喷嚏
And if anyone is ever rude to you, sneeze muffin.
谢了  瑞秋
Thanks, Rach.
你们对我真好
Hey, look, you guys are just terrific, you know?
不如你们先行退下  好让我招待几个新顾客
How about clearing out so I can get some new customers?
有流动才有商机
It's all about turnover.
乔伊
Joey.
说真的  我的咖啡什么时候上
Seriously, can I get my coffee?
抱歉  罗斯  马上来
Oh, I'm sorry, Ross. I'll get it for you right now.
让你等这么久  我送你一块松饼做补偿吧
And since I made you wait, I'll toss in a free muffin
菲比  我们想跟你谈谈
Phoebe. We would like to talk to you for a second.
好
Okay.
或许我是有点难搞
So, maybe I am a little high maintenance.
或许瑞秋是有点没个性
And maybe Rachel is a little bit of a pushover.
但你知道我们觉得你是什么吗
But you know what we decided you are?
很抱歉这么说
Yes, we are very sorry to tell you this,
但是你  菲比  是个怪人
but you, Phoebe, are flaky.
没错  我是很怪
That's true, I am flaky.
所以说你怪  你也无所谓吗
So, what, you're just, you're just okay with being flaky?
完全无所谓
Yeah, totally.
那我难搞也无所谓
Then I'm okay with being high maintenance.
那我没个性也无所谓
Yeah. And I am okay with being a pushover.
太好了  无所谓就好
That's great. Good for you guys.
我才不难搞
I am not high maintenance!
我才不是没个性
I am not a pushover!
-谁说你们是了  -你啊
- Who said you were? - You did!
我是怪人  专门乱说话
I'm flaky. I'll say anything.
甘瑟
Hey, Gunther.
你能替我一下吗  我刚接到试镜通知
Can you cover for me? I got an audition.
不行  我要去染头发
No, I'm leaving to get my hair dyed.
是吗  我喜欢你的自然色
I like your natural color.
拜托  伙计  这是个好角色
Come on man. It's a great part.
听我说  我演男主角的死党
Look, check it out. I'm the lead guy's best friend
负责在酒吧帮他占位子  你听
and I wait for him in this bar and save his seat. Listen-listen.
"抱歉  这个位子有人"
"I'm sorry, that seat's saved."
就这样
That's the whole part?
或许不是他的死党  但是...
Okay, maybe he's not his best friend. But...
得了  1小时后见
Okay, I'll see you in an hour.
天啊
Oh, man.
我绝对能拿到那个角色
I could totally get that part.
"抱歉  这个位子有人"
"I'm sorry, this seat is taken."
-抱歉  -不  我不是说你
- Excuse me. - No, no, I didn't mean you.
但你以为是真的吧
But you believed me?
我以为你在帮别人占位
I believed you were saving this seat for someone.
所以你会用我咯
So you'd hire me, right?
用你干嘛
For what?
就是说嘛  好啦  各位请注意
Exactly! All right, everybody listen up!
本店要暂停营业1小时
The coffeehouse is gonna be closed for about an hour.
什么
What?
都是为了帮助孩子们
Yeah, it's for the kids.
让孩子远离毒品
Yeah, to keep the kids off drugs.
这是本期《花花公子》的重要报导
It's a very important issue in this month's Playboy.
各位一定都看过
I'm sure you all read about it.
-那是我的笑话  -是我的
- lt's my joke. - lt's my joke.
是我的
It's my joke.
我们再吵也吵不出结果
You know, I don't think we're gonna settle this.
-让莫妮卡决定吧  -好
- Let's have Monica decide. - Yeah.
-小妹  亲爱的  -出来一下
- Hey, Mon! - Mon, get out here!
-莫妮卡  -听好了
- Monica? - Okay. Okay.
你来决定这个笑话是谁的
You have to decide whose joke this is.
为什么要我决定
Why do I have to?
因为你才能客观公正
You're the only one that can be fair.
我没法公正  你是我的男朋友
I can't be fair. You're my boyfriend.
但我是你哥哥  我们是家人
Yeah. But I'm your brother. We're family.
世上最重要的就是亲情
That's the most important thing in the world.
不要想左右她
Don't try to sway her.
只有我能让你生小孩
I'm your only chance to have a baby.
-我们开始吧  -好的
- Okay, let's go. - All right.
我们会分别说出这个笑话的由来
Okay. We'll each tell you how we came up with the joke
你再决定谁说的是实话  当然是我
...then you decide which one of us is telling the truth. Me.
-钱德勒  你先  -好
- Chandler, you go first. - Okay.
好  我是两个月前
I thought of the joke two months ago
跟史提夫吃饭时想到的
at lunch with Steve.
慢着  就是圣诞节那家伙吗
Oh, wait, is he the guy I met at Christmas?
让我说完好吗
Can I finish my story?!
你要我选你吗
You want me to pick you?
我绝对不会像那样凶你
See, I would never snap at you like that.
二个孩子
Two babies.
-请继续  -好
- Continue. - Okay.
史提夫说他去看医生
So Steve said he had to go to the doctor.
他的医生姓侯
And Steve's doctor's name is Doctor Homey.
我当时问他  "是猴子医生吗"
So I said, "Dr. Monkey?"
所以才会有猴子医生这个笑话
And that is how the whole Dr. Monkey thing came up.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我是念进化论的
Okay, look, I study evolution.
记得吧  进化论
Remember? Evolution.
猴子进化成人
Monkey into man.
况且我是博士
Plus, I'm a doctor. And...
我还养过猴子
...l had a monkey.
我是猴子博士
I'm Dr. Monkey!
这点我不跟你争
I'm not arguing with that.
好  可以了  我决定好了
All right, I've heard enough. I've made my decision.
-好的  如何  -说吧
- Okay, so what- - ? - Do tell.
你们两个都是白痴
You are both idiots.
那个笑话不但不好笑
It's not funny.
还冒犯了女性
And it's offensive to women.
还有医生  还有猴子
And doctors. And monkeys.
你们不该争笑话是谁的
You shouldn't argue over who gets credit.
你们应该去争是谁
You should argue over who gets blamed
让这世界受这种罪
for inflicting this horrible joke on the world.
别再争了
Now, let it go.
那个笑话烂透了
The joke sucks.
-那是你的笑话  -才不是
- lt's your joke. - lt is not.
-钱德勒  你在这里啊  -你好
- Oh, my God, Chandler, there you are. - Hi.
是菲比和瑞秋
Hey, it's Phoebe and Rachel.
你要不要告诉她们
Hey, why don't you tell them
你刚才说的话
what you were telling me earlier
说我并不难搞
about me not being high maintenance?
莫妮卡是个自信沉着的女性
Monica is a self- sufficient, together lady.
跟她在一起就像在度假
Being with her has been like being on a vacation.
至于所谓的难搞
And what may be perceived as high maintenance...
只是注重小细节
is merely attention to detail
和...
...and...
心灵的慷慨
generosity of spirit.
哇  不得不说
Wow. You know what?
这真是我听过最棒的假话
That is the best fake speech I think I've ever heard.
真的  我听过更棒的
Really? I've heard better.
等等  那是他自己说的
Wait, he came up with that himself.
告诉她们  钱德勒
Tell them, Chandler.
我已经词穷了  我可以复述一遍吗
I'm out of words. Should I just say the whole thing again?
我一点也不难搞
Look, I am not high maintenance!
我不是  钱德勒
I am not. Chandler!
你是有点难搞
You're a little high maintenance.
你上我的黑名单了
You are on my list!
对不起  但是你并不
Look, I'm sorry, but you're not- -
你并不好相处  但你很热情
You're not easygoing, but you're passionate.
这样很好
And that's good.
当你为小事不高兴时
And when you get upset about little things,
我会恰如其分地
I think that I'm pretty good at
帮你排解解难
making you feel better about that.
那样也很好
That's good too.
所以她们说你难搞也行
They say you're high maintenance...
但没关系  因为我喜欢...
...but it's okay, because I like...
搞定你
maintaining you.
我可没叫他说这些
I didn't even tell him to say that.
-你从黑名单除名了  -我除名了
- Alright. You're off my list. - I'm off the list.
菲比
Phoebe?
你不找我当女朋友也没关系
It's okay that you don't want me to be your girlfriend.
因为我有最棒的男朋友
I have the best boyfriend.
我突然觉得你好迷人
You know, suddenly I find you very attractive.
兄弟  试镜结果如何
Hey, buddy boy, how'd the audition go?
不好
Oh, not good. No.
我没拿到那个角色
I didn't get the part.
这里的工作也没了  所以...
And I lost my job here, so....
好惨烈的试镜
Wow, that is a bad audition.
这里的工作为什么没了
Well, how did you lose your job here?
我要去试镜
Well, I had the audition...
但甘瑟叫我留在这里顾店
but Gunther said I had to stay here and be in charge
他好去染头发
so he could go get his hair dyed.
但我还是去了  他就炒我鱿鱼
So I went anyway, and he fired me.
他大白天扔下工作去办私事
He left work in the middle of the day to do a personal errand
把一个刚工作两天的员工  留下顾店
and left you in charge when you've been working here two days?
这样不对吧
That's not right.
但是能怎么办
What are you gonna do?
乔伊  你不能就这么算了
Joey, you can't let him get away with that.
我绝不放过他
Ya know what, I won't let him get away with that.
我要去教训他
I'm gonna say something
不  我不该多事
No, I shouldn't say anything.
不  我要去教训他
No, I should say something to him.
甘瑟
Gunther?
让乔伊继续在这里打工
I want you to give Joey his job back.
-你这样解雇他一点也不...  - 好
- lt's not fair that you have to fire- -  - Okay.
-什么  -他可以继续打工
- What? - He can have his job back.
没错  他可以继续打工
That's right, he can have his job back.
很高兴我们把事情都说明白了
Glad we got that all straightened out.
好了  乔伊
There you go, Joey.
你可以继续打工了
Got your job back.
太好了  谢谢你  瑞秋
That's great. Thanks. Rachel.
不赖吧  谁没个性了
Pretty nice, huh? Now who's a pushover?
-瑞秋  你坐到我的位子了  -抱歉
- Rach, you're in my seat. - I'm sorry.
你们都没说
Hey, I never got to hear
会找谁当女朋友
who you guys would pick to be your girlfriend.
我选你  菲比
I'd pick you, Phoebe.
没错  绝对是你  菲比
Yeah, definitely you, Pheebs.
我也这么觉得
Yeah, I kind of thought.
我有一个问题
Hey. Oh, I have a question.
如果你们要找
If-if-if one of you had to pick
另外两个人当男朋友
one of the other two guys to go out with,
你们会找谁
...who would you pick?
-少来  -我拒绝回答
- No way. - I'm not answering that.
乔伊
Joey.
少来  我拒绝回答
No way, I'm not answering that.